Finding aid for the The Ohio State University Health Sciences Library Records
Medical Heritage Center
- Series IV: History (4 boxes) contains the general documents and newsletters that reference important milestones and events at the Health Sciences Library. This series is arranged alphabetically., 1933-2013
  - Annual Report, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ASK Desk Training Manual, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Auerbach Final Report, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Award Letter, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Budget Reduction Plans, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Budget Reduction Plans, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Budget Reduction Plans, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Budget Reduction Plans, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Budget Request, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Capital Funding Request, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Cartoons about HSL, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Center for Health Information, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Dedication, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Department Program Plan, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Department Program Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Departmental Budget Report, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Display Case, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Educational Services Needs Assessment, No Date (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Employee Notebook, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Funding Request, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - HEA History (File 1 of 3), 1933-1997 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - HEA History (File 2 of 3), 1933-1997 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - HEA History (File 3 of 3), 1933-1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - HEA Policies, 1990-1999 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - HEA Reorganization, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Health Sciences Library Service Bulletin, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Hospital Libraries Setting up, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - HSL: Plan of Action, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - HSL: Plan of Action (File 1 of 2), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - HSL: Plan of Action (File 2 of 2), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - HSL: Self-Study Committee, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Journal, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - KMC Reception, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Knowledge Management Center, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Letter: Temporary Suspension of Gift Donations, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Librarians’ Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Librarians’ Retreat, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Librarians’ Retreat, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Librarians’ Retreat, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Library Committee, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Library Leadership Council, 2001-2003 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Library Logo, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Library Service Guide, 1993-2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Library Services, No Date (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Logo, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Lost and Found, 1977-1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Management Council Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Membership/Subscriptions, 1996-2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Mural - Cleaning, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Mural Lights and Brochure, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - National Institutes of Health Joint Construction Grant, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - National Network of Libraries of Medicine, 1994-2001 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Nite-out Bulletins, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - NLM/AAH Leadership Fellows, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Ohio Public Health Information Literacy Training Project, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Open House, 1983-1996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Operations Review, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - OSU Health Services: Department and Faculty Hierarchy, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Party (Kathy and Pat), 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Position Descriptions, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - PR Promotional Pieces, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Preliminary Plan of Action, Autumn 1989 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Program of Requirements - Health Sciences Info Center, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Program Review: Positive Approach to Assessment, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Publicity, 1969-2003 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Rededication (File 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Rededication (File 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Rededication Materials, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Rededication Symposium 1, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rededication Symposium 2, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Rededication Symposium 3, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Reporting Line, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Retention Schedule of Record at HEA, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Self-Guided Tour of the HSL, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Steering Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Strategic Planning Report, No Date (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Suggestion Box (File 1 of 2), 1986-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Suggestion Box (File 2 of 2), 1986-1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Suggestions, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Technology, 1989-2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Telephone Directory, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Telephones, 1967-2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Thank You Note for Dr. Prior, February 1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - UHE Library (File 1 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - UHE Library (File 2 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - UHE Library (File 3 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Visiting Scholar 02, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Workplace of Choice Committee, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Series V: Media (6 boxes) contains boxes of photos and slides that mostly deal with the renovation and construction projects, but there are also staff and building photos as well. One box of this series houses digital media such as CDs, floppy disks and DVDs. This box also contains VHS recordings of the rededication ceremony., 1970-2005
  - VHS: Rededication Symposium, Tape 1: 3 Copies, April 25, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - VHS: Rededication Symposium, Tape 2: 3 Copies, April 25, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - VHS: Rededication Symposium, Tape 3: 3 Copies, April 25, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - VHS: Sample Videotape (COHI - The Council on Health Information), No Date (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - VHS: Frankenstein Event in HLRI, October 2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - DVD: The Library as Place, No Date (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - CD: Jones Staff Presentation Power Point, No Date (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - CD: Reference and Information Files, 1999-2004 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - CD: C10 Program Rev., No Date (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - CD: Murray, Prior Health, Tzagournis, Wiseman, August 2005 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - CD: Acock, Record Drawings Files, July 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - CD: Renovation Photos, 1, No Date (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - CD: Renovation Photos, 2, No Date (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - CD: Renovation Photos, 3, No Date (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - CD: Renovation Photos, 4, No Date (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - CD: OSU Photo Services, Pamela Bradigan, December 2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - CD: Randtriever Articles, Library Hi-Tech, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Floppy Disk: Facilities/Exhibit Area, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Floppy Disk: Specification For Computerized Dir. HSL, No Date (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Floppy Disk: Email and Internet Images, Vanbrimmer (Disk 1), No Date (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Floppy Disk: Email and Internet Images, Vanbrimmer (Disk 2), No Date (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Photos: Move to and from JORCS and Construction, No Date (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Photos and Drawings: Floor Plans and Building Construction, No Date (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Photos and Negatives: Staff and HSL Building, No Date (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Slides: Construction, Floor Plans and Staff, No Date (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Construction of Prior, Randtriever, 1970s (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Randtriever (2 boxes) is dedicated to the construction, history and overall understanding of the Randtriever. The Randtriever was a two-story automated book retrieval system that was part of the original construction project from the 1960’s. The Randtriever and the building were completed in 1972, but the Randtriever became a cause of concern. The automated system did not perform as intended and by 1992 it had been removed. This series is arranged alphabetically., 1967-1995
  - Advertising: Remote Storage and Building Plans, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Architects, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Articles, HEA Building, Media, Stats, Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Background Information on Randtriever, No Date (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Betty - Randtriever, No Date (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cartoons, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence about Randtriever (File 1 of 2), 1967-1991 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence about Randtriever (File 2 of 2), 1967-1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - CSUN OVIATT - Leo A Daly, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Pamphlets and Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Paper on Randtriever, 1971-1986 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Principles of Operation and Maintenance (File 1 of 2), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Principles of Operation and Maintenance (File 2 of 2), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Randtriever Articles (File 1 of 2), 1982-1988 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Randtriever Articles (File 2 of 2), 1982-1988 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Randtriever Building Maintenance Correspondence (File 1 of 2), 1976-1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Randtriever Building Maintenance Correspondence (File 2 of 2), 1976-1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Randtriever Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Randtriever Complaints, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Randtriever Early Planning, 1967-1973 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Randtriever Emergency Phase, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Randtriever Funding and Correspondence (File 1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Randtriever Funding and Correspondence (File 2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Randtriever History (File 1 of 2), 1967-1991 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Randtriever History (File 2 of 2), 1967-1991 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Randtriever In Regards to Erasmus University, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Randtriever Log, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Randtriever Maintenance and Renovations, 1986-1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Randtriever Master File Bins 4 - 7, No Date (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Randtriever Master File Bins 8 - 11, No Date (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Randtriever Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Randtriever Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Randtriever Miscellaneous (File 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Randtriever Miscellaneous (File 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Randtriever Physical Description, 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Randtriever Principles of Operation: Maintenance, No Date (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Randtriever Project, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Randtriever Removal Plans, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Randtriever Removal Plans, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Randtriever Reports, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Randtriever Schematics, 1967, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Randtriever Status Reports, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Randtriever Tests, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Randtriever Updates, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Report on Its Use, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Second Floor, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Second Floor Reconfiguration, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - TRT Report, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)